Patrick Brown

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

SUMMARY

6+ years experience developing user experience deliverables including:

User Research: Identify user information needs via usability studies, as well as through interviews with SMEs and end-users.

Prototyping: Developing low to high fidelity interactive models to gather user validation, stakeholder acceptance, and guide engineering implementation.

Information Architecture: Combine qualitative and datadriven techniques to develop site maps, layouts, content, and taxonomies.

EXPERIENCE

Echo Global Logistics

Senior Software Designer (Oct 2015 - Present)

Developed a pattern library to coordinate design systems across several enterprise applications.

Designed a suite of sales focused tools for internal client representatives.

Supported legacy systems with iterative, user focused research engagements.

Navigated organization to achieve operational improvements.

Tenth Magnitude

Design Consultant (Feb 2015 - Aug 2015)

Supported engineering teams with design asset production.

Product and system design for a complex payment and invoicing system.

Organized and debugged legacy front end code for responsive refactoring.

The Field Museum

Digital Media Specialist (Aug 2009 - Jan 2015)

Developed quantitative metrics for social engagement.

Coordinated content development between public relations and digital departments.

Contributed to online publish platform user experience.

(773) 710-8411

pdbrown@protonmail.com

PORTFOLIO

patrickbrown.design

SKILLS

Adobe Creative Cloud

Axure

CSS

Framer

HTML

InVision

JavaScript

Microsoft Office 365

OmniGraffle

Sketch

UXPin

Version Control (Git, SVN)

Zeplin

AFFILIATIONS

AIGA

Creative Mornings

Code for America

IxDA

EDUCATION

Columbia College Chicago

B.A.- With High Honors Interactive Arts and Media